48 Christmas Wishes is a family, tv movie film directed by Marco Deufemia.
Holiday magic has never gleamed brighter as Santa’s Elves head out on an adventure to bring every boy and girl their
Christmas wish while also bringing a family back together in this heartfelt Christmas movie from Gaumont.
After accidentally destroying a bag of Christmas wishes from a small town on the eve of Christmas Eve, two
junior elves learn that if even one wish goes unfulfilled, Christmas could be extinguished forever.
For the first time in their lives, the elves Mindy and Cam venture out of the
North Pole and sneak into Minnedoza to collect the lost wishes.
Along the way they enlist the help of young Blake, whose family has a
difficult time celebrating Christmas since his father died.
With their deadline fast approaching, Mindy and Cam have only
one more wish to find…but whose could it be?
It’s up to Mindy and Cam to find out and save Christmas!
Lara, played by Madeline Leon.
Blake, played by Liam MacDonald.
Mindy, played by Clara Kushnir.
Emma, played by Elizabeth Ellsworth.
Sammy, played by Maya Franzoi.
Business Man, played by Matt Schichter.
Many Christmas stories have been adapted to feature films and TV specials,
and have been broadcast and repeated many times on television.
Since the popularization of home video in the 1980s, these films are sold
and re-sold every year during the holiday shopping season.
Many television networks, film studios, and production companies, such as cable television channels Hallmark and Lifetime, produce and
release new Christmas-themed films every year during or around December, all with variations of similar plots and themes.
Additionally, films revolving around the Nativity story of Christmas are regularly
produced such as The Nativity Story (2006) and The Star (2017).
One film that has become the flashpoint for "Is this a Christmas movie or not?" debates is Die Hard (1988), with some viewing the film as a
Christmas movie intertwined with an action genre setting or a film that is simply set around the Christmas and holiday season.
The tone is emotional.